var hockey = [
	{
		front: "Gulls",
		back: "San Diego"
	}, {
		front: "Ducks",
		back: "Anaheim"
	}, {
		front: "Kings",
		back: "Los Angeles"
	},{
		front: "Sharks",
		back: "San Jose"
	}, {
		front: "Red Wings",
		back: "Detroit"
	}, {
		front: "Rangers",
		back: "New York"
	}, {
		front: "Blackhawks",
		back: "Chicago"
	}, {
		front: "Golden Knights",
		back: "Las Vegas"
	}, {
		front: "Stars",
		back: "Dallas"
	}, {
		front: "Coyotes",
		back: "Arizona"
	}, {
		front: "Penguins",
		back: "Pittsburgh"
	}, {
		front: "Bruins",
		back: "Boston"
	}, {
		front: "Predators",
		back: "Nashville"
	}
];

module.exports = hockey;